thebestdealyet.com 2016-11-03

# Privacy Policy

Our Privacy Policy **WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS:**

The Best Deal Yet takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

The federal government and technology industry have developed practical tips to help you guard against Internet fraud, secure your computer and protect your personal information. 

**How The Best Deal Yet Uses Your Personal Information:**

This policy covers how The Best Deal Yet treats personal information that The Best Deal Yet collects and receives, including information related to your past use of The Best Deal Yet products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This privacy policy only applies to The Best Deal Yet 

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE:**

The Best Deal Yet collects personal information when you register with The Best Deal Yet, when you use The Best Deal Yet products or services, when you visit The Best Deal Yet pages or the pages of certain The Best Deal Yet partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. The Best Deal Yet may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 

When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, ZIP code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. 

The Best Deal Yet collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners and Advertisers 

The Best Deal Yet automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, The Best Deal Yet cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request. 

The Best Deal Yet uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

**INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE**

The Best Deal Yet does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with The Best Deal Yet under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help The Best Deal Yet communicate with you about offers from The Best Deal Yet and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of The Best Deal Yet terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. We transfer information about you if The Best Deal Yet is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, The Best Deal Yet will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

The Best Deal Yet displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria�for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area. 

The Best Deal Yet does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. The Best Deal Yet advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies). 

The Best Deal Yet works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business. For more information regarding providers of products or services that you've requested please read our detailed reference links. 

**COOKIES:**

The Best Deal Yet may set and access The Best Deal Yet cookies on your computer. 

The Best Deal Yet lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to The Best Deal Yet cookies. 

The Best Deal Yet uses web beacons to access The Best Deal Yet cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with The Best Deal Yet products and services. Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences 

**GENERAL:**

You can edit your The Best Deal Yet Account Information, including your marketing preferences, at any time. 

New categories of marketing communications might be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive. 

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the The Best Deal Yet service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the The Best Deal Yet Newsletter, that are considered part of your The Best Deal Yet account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. 

You can delete your The Best Deal Yet account by visiting our Account Deletion page. Please click here to read about information that might possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted. 

**CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY:**

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. 

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY:**

The Best Deal Yet may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your The Best Deal Yet account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**PAYMENT POLICY:** In some cases The Best Deal Yet may need to verify your a real person to comply with various laws we may also ask you to verify your account at any time this information is not passed to any third party's. 

**QUESTIONS AND SUGGESTIONS:**

If you have questions, suggestions, or wish to make a complaint, please complete a feedback form or you can contact us at: Please Use the contact us button above or email us at [ Send Email](mailto:bestdyet@gmail.com?subject=The%20Best%20Deal%20Yet%20-%20Contact)
